Workers United Records 6284
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United Records
1980-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United
6284
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Articles, reports, pamphlets, correspondence, records.
8791373
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 09, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Workers United
8791373
- ACTWU Worker Education Project, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Part 1 of 3
- ACTWU Worker Education Project (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Part 2 of 3
- ACTWU Worker Education Project (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Worker Education Program Christmas Party, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Actuaremos Siempre (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Actwamos, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers Union Education Programs and Sample Materials, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Arrival of Columbus in America and What Happened After That (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Asian Pacific Islander Caucus Bylaws (3 copies), 2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A Brief History of ACTWU, ILGWU and UNITE, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- B-1 A Brief History of the ILGWU (Box 1, Folder 12)
- CHALK The First 10 Years, 2004-2014 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Chapter 2: Teaching Approach (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Chinatown Garment Industry Study Local 23-25 ILGWU, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Chinatown Manpower Project Inc. Workplace Literature Program Book #1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Chinatown Manpower Project Inc. Workplace Literacy Program Book #2, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- A Christmas Present: A Play in Two Acts (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Class of Jackie Bain, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Coalition for Immigration Reform, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CODE Tech Curri Man, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- District 65 UAW Consortium (Box 1, Folder 22)
- District 65 UAW Consortium (Box 1, Folder 23)
  2 of 3
- District 65 UAW Consortium (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Dot Patterns (Box 1, Folder 25)
  several copies
- Education for Education Careers, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- English in the Garment Shops (Box 1, Folder 27)
  3 copies
- ESL Curriculum (Box 1, Folder 28)
- ESL Curriculum (Box 1, Folder 29)
- ESL Curriculum (Box 1, Folder 30)
- ESL Curriculum for Sewing (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Copy 1
- ESL Curriculum for Sewing (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Copy 2
- ESL Curriculum for Sewing (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Copy 3
- ESL Curso de Verano, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Agosto
- ESL Essays (Box 1, Folder 35)
- ESL Exercises (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Evelyn Dubrow, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Excerpts from Everyday Life, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Excerpts from Student Magazines, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Fordham Journal, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Fordham Library Morning Intensive Class, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- From Theory to Practice: A Set of Garment-Related ESL Curriculum, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  copy 1, (1 of 2)
- From Theory to Practice: A Set of Garment-Related ESL Curriculum (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Copy 1 (2 of 2)
- From Theory to Practice: a Set of Garment Related ESL Curriculum (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Copy 2, (2 of 2)
- From Theory to Practice: A Set of Garment-Related ESL Curriculum, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  1 of 2 (copy 2)
- From Theory to Practice: A Set of Garment-Related ESL Curriculum (Box 2, Folder 7)
  2 of 2 (copy 3)
- From Theory to Practice: A Set of Garment Related ESL Curriculum (Box 2, Folder 8)
  1 of 2 (copy 3)
- Garment Workers' Center Workplace Literacy Class, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Summer
- The Global Factory: Course Overview, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The Global Economy Chapter 10, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- The Global Factory: ESL Curriculum (Box 2, Folder 12)
  3 Copies
- The Global Factory: Journey of a Blouse (Box 2, Folder 13)
- The Global Factory System: Where are the Jobs Going? (Box 2, Folder 14)
  2 copies
- Health and Safety Timeline for ESL at the Workplace (Box 2, Folder 15)
- I Remember..An Oral History of China, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Adult Basic Education Class
- Health and Safety, Lesson 2, "The Hokey Pokey" Continues (Box 2, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
- ILGWU 1912 Lawrence Strike Lesson (Box 2, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Adult Literacy Program (Box 2, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Campaign for Justice (Box 2, Folder 21)
- ILGWU The Chinatown Garment Industry Study (Box 2, Folder 22)
- ILGWU Catalogue of Literature (Box 2, Folder 23)
- ILGWU Complete Worker-Family Education Program, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- ILGWU Complete Worker-Family Education Program, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- ILGWU Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry (Box 2, Folder 26)
- ILGWU The Consortium Adult Literacy Program (Box 2, Folder 27)
  1 of 2 (copy 1)
- ILGWU The Consortium Adult Literacy Program, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  2 of 2 (copy 1)
- ILGWU Consortium Adult Literacy Program (Box 2, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Consortium Adult Literacy Program (Box 2, Folder 30)
  2 of 2 (copy 2)
- ILGWU documents 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- ILGWU documents, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- ILGWU documents and case study, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- ILGWU ESL AIDS Curriculum (Box 3, Folder 4)
- ILGWU ESL Classes, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- ILGWU ESL Lesson: Ellis Island, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- ILGWU The Fruits of Our Struggle (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ILGWU "Games for the Classroom", 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Health Care Curriculum (Box 3, Folder 9)
- ILGWU History Documents (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Hot off the Press, and ESL Magazine ILGWU, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Immigration Project: Amnesty Education Program 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Immigration Project Anti-Employment Discrimination Work, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Immigration Project: Promotion of Citizenship/Naturalization, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Industrial Homework Lessons for ESL Classes (Box 3, Folder 15)
- ILGWU: Justice, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Labor Unity, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Lessons on the Topic of Immigration (Box 3, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Locals, Joint Boards, District Councils, Area Offices & Subordinate Organizations (Box 3, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Mademoiselle (Box 3, Folder 20)
- ILGWU On Your Own English Level 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- ILGWU On Your Own in English Level 2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- ILGWU On Your Own English Level 4 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- ILGWU Oral Histories, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- ILGWU Our Past, Our Present, Our Lives, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- ILGWU Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Rainbows, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Rainbows, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- ILGWU Students in Action, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Student Magazine, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- ILGWU Students on the Move (Box 3, Folder 31)
- ILGWU Union Curriculum Package, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- ILGWU Union Curriculum Package, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  copy 2
- ILGWU Union Curriculum Package, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- ILGWU "Union Made", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ILGWU "We've Come a Long Way Baby", 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Worker Family Education Program English Level IV, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program A-Continued (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Lawrence Strike Lesson, 3 copies
- ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program Chinatown Site Local 23-25 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Worker Family Education Program Curriculum Guide, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Workers Family Education Program Curriculum Guide, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Workers' Rights Handbook (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Immigrants' Struggles In the USA, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  (2 of 2)
- Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  (1 of 2)
- Impartial Chairman Hearing, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Info Packet on the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Info Packet on the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Info Packet on the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Japan/Hong Kong - Japan Institute of Labor, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Japan Institute of Labor Invitation Program, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Labor Institute of Public Affairs, Television Skills Workshop, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  New York
- Labor Notes' Workshop (Box 4, Folder 20)
- The Lawrence Strike (Box 4, Folder 21)
  by Mastrodonato
- Learning About Labor Issues and Workplace Control (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Learning About Labor Issues and Workplace Control (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Learning About Labor Issues and Workplace Control (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Learning About Labor Issues and Workplace Control Francine Moccio Ph.D. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  copy 3
- Life Sketches, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- List of Employers who Employ GIDC Graduates (Box 4, Folder 27)
- List of Events for the 100th Anniversary Commemoration of the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- List of UNITE Shops in the Garment District (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Live and Learn! ESL Labor History Curriculum (Box 4, Folder 30)
  copy 1
- Live and Learn! ESL Labor History Curriculum (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Live and Learn! ESL Labor History Curriculum (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Luchando con la Vida, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- MEMO Re: Garment Industry Facts, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- MEMO: Speakers, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- MEMO Teachers from Maureen Re: Where are the jobs going?, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- My Family ESL Class Level 1 Spring, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board ILGWU Education Program, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Nifty Teaching Ideas: Games, Role-Playing, Theater (Box 5, Folder 7)
- NYC Central Labor Council AFL-CIO Apa Outreach, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- The NYC Garment Industry (Box 5, Folder 9)
- On Focus (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Oral Histories The Words: A Class Project, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Organizing and Representing Undocumented Workers NLG Seminars, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Our Family (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Our Memories (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Our Mural of Cultures (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Partnering for Health with May Ying Chen (Box 5, Folder 16)
- The Paycheck (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Personal Information - Interviews (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Piece Rate ESL Curriculum (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Poemas de amor, GED Class, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- "Proving Herself" Language Activities (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Shop Talk: The New York ACTWU Working Student Newsletter, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- So You Don't Like Your Job (Box 5, Folder 23)
- The St. Agnus Cookbook (Box 5, Folder 24)
- The St. Agnes Journal, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Stories from the class of 2003, UNITE (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Students in Action, ILGWU, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- The Students of Unite Speak Out (Box 5, Folder 28)
- The Students of Unite Speak Out - Magazine Originals (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Teacher's Notes Unit III (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Teacher's Notes Unit III (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Teacher's Notes Unit III (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Teaching Reading Through Oral Histories (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Teacher Training Plans, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Teacher Training Plans, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- To the Pace of the Tempo, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- The Triangle Fire Project, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- "Turning Paperwork into a Lesson" ESL Curriculum (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Unemployment: A New World Order (Box 6, Folder 4)
  part 1 of 2, copy 3
- Unemployment: A New World Order (Box 6, Folder 5)
  part 2 of 2, copy 3
- Unemployment: A New World Order (Box 6, Folder 6)
  1 of 2, copy 1
- Unemployment: A New World Order (Box 6, Folder 7)
  2 of 2, copy 1
- Unemployment: A New World Order (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Unemployment: A New World Order (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Specific Lessons
- Unemployment: A New World Order (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Teacher's Notes
- UNITE Annual Art Exhibition, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Union Basics ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program A-continued (Box 6, Folder 12)
- UNITE Chinatown Level 1 Curriculum (Box 6, Folder 13)
- UNITE Combining Computers with ESL, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- UNITE ESL Lessons on the Topic of Immigration (Box 6, Folder 15)
- UNITE HERE!, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- UNITE Immigration Project, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- UNITE! Newsletters, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- UNITE! New Steps of the Union (Box 6, Folder 19)
- UNITE! New Steps of the Union (Box 6, Folder 20)
- UNITE! Reflections, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- UNITE! Students in Action Rainbows (Box 6, Folder 22)
- UNITE! Workers' Education Department (Box 6, Folder 23)
  suggested curriculum list
- UNITE! Worker's Education Department (Box 6, Folder 24)
- UNITE! Worker-Family Education Program, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- UNITE! Worker-Family Education Program, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- UNITE! Worker-Family Education Program, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Technical Curriculum Manual, copy 1
- UNITE! Worker-Family Education Program, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Technical Curriculum Manual, copy 2
- UNITE Worker-Family Education Program, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Technical Curriculum Manual, copy 3
- We Are Workers and Students ACTWU (Box 6, Folder 30)
- We're All in this Together!, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Worker Unity: Organizing and Representing Undocumented Workers (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Your OSHA Rights (Box 6, Folder 33)
- "Your Rights at Work" (Box 6, Folder 34)
  and ESL Workbook
- Your Rights at Work (Box 6, Folder 35)
  and ESL Workbook, 3 copies
- ACTWU Worker Education Project ESL Materials Manual: Intro & Immigrant Experience (Box 7, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Worker Education Project ESL Materials Manual: Transportation (Box 7, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Worker Education Project ESL Materials Manual: Workplace (Box 7, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Worker Education Project ESL Materials Manual: Unemployment/Job Hunting (Box 7, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Worker Education Project ESL Materials Manual: Housing (Box 7, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Worker Education Project ESL Materials Manual: Health & Safety (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Labor Studies in the ESL and ABE Classroom (Box 7, Folder 7)
- ESL Classes @ H. S. of Fashion: Technical/ESL Curriculum Notes (Box 7, Folder 8)
- ILGWU "Union" Curriculum (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Sexual Harassment Lesson (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Background of the Worker-Family Education Program (Box 7, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Union Basics ESL Lesson, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- The Steward: The Person in the Middle (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Unite Workers' Education Department Suggested Curriculum (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Unit II - Workers' Compensation and Your Rights: "Maria's News Manny Hurt His Back" (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Unit III - Discrimination and Your Rights: "Fatima's Dilemma, Hak Gets Laid Off" (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Unit IV - Unions and Your Rights: "The Union Card, The Union Meeting" (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Unit V - Other Workplace Right: "Abla Gets Fired, The Unemployment Office, Baby it's Cold in Here" (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Health Care Curriculum for ILGWU Members (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Puppet Theatre (Box 7, Folder 20)
- New Jersey Council, UNITE Citizenship Workshop, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Amnesty Education Program Announcements in "El Diario" (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Enforcement Guidance on Remedies Available to Undocumented Workers (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Citizenship Packet (Box 7, Folder 24)
- American College Testing (ACT) Citizenship Test, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Immigration Project Celebration of New Citizens, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Amnesty Education Program Closing Ceremony, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- SLIAG English Language Proposal, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- SLIAG Proposal: Fiscal Year, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- INS Certificate of Attorney General Recognition, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- SLIAG Contract: Fiscal Year, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- SLIAG Audit: Fiscal Year, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- SLIAG Continuation Proposal: Fiscal Year 1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- SLIAG Community Development Agency Back-Up Information to Fiscal Year 1990 Budget (Box 7, Folder 34)
- SLIAG Community Development Agency Direct Funding, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- SLIAG Contract: Fiscal Year 1990 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- SLIAG Audit: Fiscal Year, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- SLIAG Continuation Proposal: Fiscal Year 1989, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- SLIAG Close Out, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- SLIAG Contract: Fiscal Year, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- SLIAG Outreach Funding Application, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- SLIAG Community Development Budget, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- SLIAG Audit: Fiscal Year 1991 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- SLIAG Continuation Proposal: Fiscal Year 1992 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- SLIAG Contract: Fiscal Year 1992 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- ILGWU Immigration Project Correspondence, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- SLIAG Contract: Fiscal Year 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Employment Anti-Discrimination Project Proposal, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Curriculum Packet About Immigration-Related Job Discrimination, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Employment Anti-Discrimination Project Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Employment Anti-Discrimination Project Contract Fiscal Year 1992, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Employment Anti-Discrimination Project Grant Reports and Vouchers Fiscal Year 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Employment Anti-Discrimination Project Proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Contract Language for Projecting Immigrant Workers (Box 8, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Responses to Anti-Immigrant Sentiments, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- UNITE Immigration Project (Box 8, Folder 5)
- UNITE Request to Finish Fiscal Year 1996 Grant, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Office of Special Counsel Request of Immigration Project Proposals, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Office of Special Counsel Immigration Project Grant Reports, 1995-2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Community Anti-Discrimination Public Education, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Office of Special Counsel Grant Application: Fiscal Year 1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Office of Special Counsel Immigration Project Grant Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Immigration Project: Chinese Immigration Cases, 1989-2003 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  To make labels, general query pp.1-10, 21-36
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  To make labels, general query pp.43-100
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  To make labels, general query pp.101-188, 197-199
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  To make labels, general query pp.237-299
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  To make labels, general query pp.300-370
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  To make labels, general query pp.371-409
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  To make labels, general query pp.410-459
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  To make labels, general query pp.460-500
- UNITE! Immigration Project Labels, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  To make labels, labels 98 query
- Unite! Immigration Project, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Unite Publication Immigration Articles, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry, 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Speech by NYC Mayor David Dinkens, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Office of Refugee Resettlement Meeting Agenda, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Resolution Concerning New York City Sweatshops, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Arbitration Awards, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Affiliates Assistance Funds, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Post 9-11 Funding: Legal Services for Affected Chinese Community, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Unite! Agenda 2003 for Caregivers for the Disabled (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Workers Unite Support for Haiti Earthquake, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Some Early ILGWU History in Pictures (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Montero v. Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Sanchez FOIA Case (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Decision of the Appeal Tribunal on Herbert Novoa, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Ramos FOIA Case Confidential, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Ramos FOIA Case Confidential, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Ramos FOIA Case Confidential, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 40)